Good evening, and welcome to our evening news broadcast
Today, we're focusing on the latest developments in politics, particularly in the state of Telangana
First up, a new report suggests that millionaires who threaten to leave their home countries due to high taxes may not actually follow through with their plans
According to Phil White, a British millionaire, "Tax the rich" placards were held next to the Congress center during the World Economic Forum (WEF) annual meeting in Davos on January 18, 2023
However, it appears that these threats may be nothing more than empty posturing
In related news, Shekhar Koirala, a prominent figure within the Nepali Congress party, has been making headlines with a series of high-profile meetings
This has sparked speculation about the potential troubles facing Nepal's government
Meanwhile, in the United States, Jesse Watters has made a statement regarding Governor Gavin Newsom's claims about a phone call between the two
While Watters maintains that Newsom was not lying, the governor has responded by saying, "Well, see you in court, buddy
" This exchange highlights the ongoing political tensions in the country
In other news, the export of white rice from Kakinada has come to a halt due to efforts to combat smuggling
This development is significant, as it affects the distribution of cereal through ration shops in Andhra Pradesh
Finally, the Congress party has called for the inclusion of socio-economic factors in the upcoming census, with the goal of breaking the 50% ceiling in the OBC quota
This move reflects the ongoing efforts to address issues of inequality and social justice in Indian politics
That's all for now
Thank you for joining us tonight
We hope you have a great rest of your evening!